[
  {    "Recommendations" : "اختبار واحد",                  
    "stepControl" : "step1",
    "Questions" : [
      { "Type": "FreeText", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["الرياض"]},
      { "Type": "RadioButton", "Question": "كم يبلغ طول جبال الهملايا", "Answer":["الرياض", "القاهرة"]},
      { "Type": "select", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["مليون كم مربع", "مائة مليار كم مربع"]}
    ]},
  {    "Recommendations" : "اختبار واحد",                  
    "stepControl" : "step1",
    "Questions" : [
      { "Type": "FreeText", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["الرياض"]},
      { "Type": "RadioButton", "Question": "كم يبلغ طول جبال الهملايا", "Answer":["الرياض", "القاهرة"]},
      { "Type": "select", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["مليون كم مربع", "مائة مليار كم مربع"]}
    ]},
  {    "Recommendations" : "اختبار واحد",                  
    "stepControl" : "step1",
    "Questions" : [
      { "Type": "FreeText", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["الرياض"]},
      { "Type": "RadioButton", "Question": "كم يبلغ طول جبال الهملايا", "Answer":["الرياض", "القاهرة"]},
      { "Type": "select", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["مليون كم مربع", "مائة مليار كم مربع"]}
    ]},
  {    "Recommendations" : "اختبار واحد",                  
    "stepControl" : "step1",
    "Questions" : [
      { "Type": "FreeText", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["الرياض"]},
      { "Type": "RadioButton", "Question": "كم يبلغ طول جبال الهملايا", "Answer":["الرياض", "القاهرة"]},
      { "Type": "select", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["مليون كم مربع", "مائة مليار كم مربع"]}
    ]},
  {    "Recommendations" : "اختبار واحد",                  
    "stepControl" : "step1",
    "Questions" : [
      { "Type": "FreeText", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["الرياض"]},
      { "Type": "RadioButton", "Question": "كم يبلغ طول جبال الهملايا", "Answer":["الرياض", "القاهرة"]},
      { "Type": "select", "Question": "ماهي عاصمة المملكة العربية السعودية", "Answer":["مليون كم مربع", "مائة مليار كم مربع"]}
    ]},
    {
      "Recommendations" : "شكرا لتواصلكم معنا .....",                  
      "stepControl" : "Completed",
      "Questions" : []            
     }
]